This browser can answer your emails,
organize your calendar, do your
shopping, automate repetitive tasks, and
even help you start a new business. Last
month, the CEO of Perplexity gave me
early access, and I've been testing it
ever since. So, here are the most
impressive things that Comet can do. So,
the main thing about Comet is this
assistant right here. You can open it
either by clicking the assistant button
in the top right or by the keyboard
shortcut option A. And this opens the
assistant that can interact with any
website that you're on. The first thing
I want to show you is how it can manage
your browser tabs. So I can say, "Open
the last 15 browser tabs from my search
history." So maybe you want to resume
your work and you want to quickly open
what you were just working on. It can do
that autonomously. See, my hands are not
touching the keyboard and it's opening
the tabs for me, which is pretty insane.
Now, even more OP than opening tabs is
organizing and closing tabs, right? So
let's say you want to do some productive
work and you have a bunch of Twitter
tabs opened. You can just say, "Close
all of my Twitter tabs." And let's be
honest, all of us have this problem of
having too many browser tabs open. And
boom, just like that, all of them were
closed. But if you think this is
impressive, you have no idea what's
coming. Because if you're still not
using an AI browser, you're going to
fall behind. Now, comet can do even more
advanced actions like this. For example,
on Shopify, it can help you set up a
Shopify store so you can start your own
e-commerce business. You can literally
start a side hustle with the help of
Comet. can help you fill it out, pick a
store design, help you fill out the
copywriting, the products, the layout.
Guys, this is insane. Like, your
imagination is really the limit. And
what's really crazy is that this is the
worst it will be. These AI browsers are
only going to get better. Imagine how
bad KGBD was when it came out, right?
How much better it is now. The same is
going to happen to AI browsers. In 6
months, in 12 months, they'll be
infinitely better than they are now.
That's why you have to start using them
today. Another powerful feature within
Comet is the voice mode. So, let's open
a new assistant window here. And by
clicking on this blue button in the
bottom right, you can enable voice mode.
Hey, comet. What can you see?
>> I can see the content of the web page
you're currently on right now. You're on
a page about Comet browser.
>> Okay. What about now? What website am I
on? What am I looking at?
>> You're on a GitHub page for a project
called Claude Code by Anthropic.
>> So, obviously there's infinite ways you
can use the voice, right? It can help
you set up new GitHub repositories
basically working as your real-time
assistant, right? It can see what you
see. It can do web search. It can tell
you what you should do. If you encounter
an error, it will see that error as
well. It is very, very OP. Another very
useful thing that Comet can do is help
you plan your trips. So, for example,
I'm going to New York in the next few
days. Which, by the way, if you're from
New York, message me on Instagram and we
can make something happen. But you can
say, find the best flights from New York
City to Prague in the next 7 days. And
Comet can absolutely do that. So, it
will search it up. Boom. Skyscreen and
Google flights. and it found several
flights in this price range that are
either direct or with one stop. Now in
the bottom right you might notice
another button and this is the
screenshot button which comes in super
handy for translation for example. So
here I want to set up the quen free API
key and you know this is Chinese because
it's Alibaba. So I'm just going to take
a screenshot and I'm going to screenshot
the first few steps. I'm going to say
translate to English. Boom. It will read
the attached file and it will give me
the steps in English. How to set up quen
coder. Pretty pretty impressive. Another
interesting thing you can do with the
screenshot is basically play geogesser.
So I'm going to take a screenshot of
here. Let's see if it recognizes where
I'm at. I'll say where is this located.
Okay. So obviously this is the statue of
liberty but I wasn't showing it but it
recognized it. This view is from the
waterfront near the statue of liberty.
That's pretty impressive because I
wasn't showing the statue itself. I was
just showing some water and a pier. The
screenshot functionality can also help
you understand complex diagrams. Right?
So I can say what am I looking at here?
Help me understand. You're looking at a
technology architecture of
infrastructure diagram for customer
service management system. Another use
case for this is finding a specific
product, right? Maybe you like some
shoes and you want to find specifically
where they sell them. Obviously, here
the link is, but let's say you're on a
website where there's no link. Help me
find where to buy these shoes,
especially for women. This would be a
very OP use case. Wait, can it draw?
Okay, so guys, this is insane. I was
just randomly testing TL Draw and I told
Comet to draw a circle. It generated
image. Okay, I was like, okay, that's
pretty good, but not that impressive.
and I said put it into TJ draw. It ran
into error because it different file
type but then it switched it up and it
did the URL and now it's inside of a
teal draw. That's insane. Let me show
you another one. Now add a blue
rectangle. Okay, so let's see if it can
add a blue rectangle. There it is. It's
generating the image. Okay, here we have
it. So now it's taking control. When you
see this blue outline, it's taking
control over the browser and can do
stuff for me. It can click buttons. So
see now file tab not allowed. So it will
choose a different way to upload it.
maybe with the URL. Boom. And there it
is. It just uploaded the blue rectangle
into my canvas. Guys, we really are
living in the future. Now, ironically,
since Comet is a AI agent, it can also
improve the prompts that you sent into
AI. So, I can say, "Make sure to rewrite
this prompt like a senior professional
prompt engineer would so that it
actually helps me build an AI SAS app."
Boom. And now I'm having AI improve my
prompts for AI. Okay. So, it wrote the
prompt and say, "Good. Now, please
change it in the text input field. You
know, I don't want it to just write the
prompt. I want it to actually go take
control of my browser. There it is. And
rewrite it, you know. So, I can see the
text input field. Okay. So, first need
to There it is. It just replaced it.
Now, a great feature within perplexity
is the keyboard shortcuts. So, if you're
using comet, you need to start using
these as well. You can create custom
shortcuts for basically anything, right?
So, there are a few shortcuts built in,
right? Such as sonar, GBD5, teach me
comet. But there are two new shortcuts I
added myself that you should absolutely
steal. First one is /ws and this is
browse the web answering short.
Something I find myself repeating many
many times per day. It just appends it
after every single prompt. Right? Then
slash rate. This one is more advanced
and it basically finds the exact
currency rate up to six digits for any
currencies conversion rates. Then it
uses code. So it writes custom Python to
perform the math for that conversion
because you don't want to do math in the
LLMs, right? They predict the next
token. It's very unreliable. Instead,
you want the LMS to write a piece of
code that does the math. Another use
case is filling out Google forms or
surveys. So, for example, let's say
you're applying to jobs, right? You fill
out 30 questions. So, instead of doing
that manually, you just speak to it for
20 30 seconds, give it the most
essential info about yourself, maybe
upload your CV and actually Comet will
fill out the Google form for you. Now,
since Comet is developed by Perplexity,
it can very easily automate your search.
It can do deep research for you. It can
summarize your Twitter notifications,
look up recent updates of software that
you're using, any type of browser search
that you might need to do manually.
Comet can do that for you automatically.
You can also use Comet while watching
YouTube, explain stuff, you know, ask
questions during the video. It's a
really great way to learn things much
faster than you would otherwise. Now,
since Comet can easily use Google Maps,
it can also help you find new leads,
right? So, maybe you want HVAC
businesses in a certain area. Whatever
business you have, it can go onto the
web and find new leads for your business
and help you start drafting cold emails
to reach them out. I mean, again,
imagination is really the only
bottleneck here. Now, inside of the
email is where things get super
interesting. Comet can help you find
unimportant answered emails. It can give
you a summary of all the emails from
last 48 hours. It can help you write
responses to those emails. It can look
for attachments that you might have
missed. Stuff that again, you can do
manually, but it would take a few
minutes. Instead, it's just one sentence
to comment and it can do that for you.
And it gets even better when we go to
Google calendar where it can help you
prepare for meetings, give you a summary
of all upcoming events, move stuff
around. I mean guys, this is really
automating a lot of the boring parts of
knowledge work. It's not automating
jobs. It's automating the repetitive
boring parts of jobs so that you can do
the high leverage creative stuff. Boom.
So here I said, help me prepare for the
meetings in my next 48 hours. It finds
the meetings, finds the Google calls for
those events and it starts helping me
prepare. So here I told it to create a
new Google doc. Boom. Opens a new tab,
new Google doc right away. And it helps
me start preparing for a specific event,
right? So I asked it about the ads and
solving call because believe it or not,
my YouTube channel is still not
monetized. If somebody is watching this
from Google, please put me in touch.
Somebody high up because I'm losing
thousands of dollars a month. So if you
know someone high up on the YouTube team
or the AdSense team, please put me in
contact. But let's see if Comet can help
me out prepare for this meeting I have
about AdSense. And again, it can
interact with the UI. So it can do
anything you yourself can do. You know,
click stuff, go into settings, create
docs, open new tabs, write stuff in a
dog, extract action items, give you
summaries of Google Docs. Yeah, it can
do a lot. And anytime you don't like
what it's doing, you can just interrupt
it and tell it what to change so that
you can point it on the right track.
Now, to be honest, there are dozens of
other things Comet can do, such as
shopping, right? It can find the right
things, find promo codes and coupons. It
can help you plan trips. So maybe you're
on a road trip and what's the fastest
way from getting from New York to
Philadelphia and you want to stop at
three different McDonald's, whatever. It
can help you plan that trip. It can
check people's early life on Wikipedia
if you want to know more about a person.
It can also help you respond to your
Tinder matches and help you step up your
dating game. It can also QA test your
entire website. So, if you're a web
developer, you know, if you're building
your own startup like myself, you want
to make sure all the buttons work, the
UI works, that you know, it's easy to
navigate. You can use Comet as a QA
tester instead of paying a full-time
person to do that with spreadsheets.
That's another great thing. It can do
Excel formulas, Google Sheets formulas,
help you organize your spreadsheets,
help you fill out the data, lots of
useful spreadsheet actions, and then it
can also help you find clips. Maybe you
see a clip on Twitter and you want to
find a full podcast. It can help you do
that. Anything that you yourself can do
in the browser, comet can help you do.
So this is what I mean when I say that
AI browsers are the future because all
software verticals will be disrupted
with AI first alternatives. The same
goes for productivity and task
management which is what I'm building
with vectal. You can use boring outdated
tools like to-doist, ClickUp, notion.
They're they're fine. They're okay. But
why would you do that when you can use
Vectal? Plus you can move your entire
team over to Vectal. give custom prompts
to every single team member so that all
of the AI agents, no matter which model
they're using, know what each person on
the team is doing. Plus, if you have
Vectoral Pro, you get unlimited access
to GBD5. That's right. Everyone who gets
Vectoral Pro, gets unlimited GBD5. Plus,
you get access to all the other features
such as idea inbox, tasks, notes,
calendar, and the newly launched
workflows. So, if you're someone who
likes to be hyperproductive and if you
want to instantly boost the productivity
of everyone on your team, go to Vectori
and give it a shot. If you just sit down
for 10 minutes and actually move your
tasks over to Vectal, I promise you
won't look back. With that being said,
thank you guys for watching and I wish
you a wonderful, productive week.